<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ET et Sidus</title>
    <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ET et Sidus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:04:38 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://elliottsao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Hugo site Plan</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/outline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:04:38 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/outline/</guid>
      <description>Reasons to use this site In general, as a Health Data Analyst and current research student in the field of public health informatics (epidemiology), I have full interests in terms of data science related programming languages and skills, therefore I wanna build a free online blog site to record all experiences, error message and others. This Hugo blog is the first stage, next stage is Django skill that I am actually learning now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to select a Machine Learning algorithm</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:37:17 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/ml/</guid>
      <description>At First - Algorithms for an ML beginner This post is mainly written for ML beginners (ie., myself). It is really confused to select an appropriate algorithm for any current case.
ML algorithms can be generally divided into Supervised learning, Unsupervised learning, Semi-Supervised learning and Reinforcement.
Supervised Learning Supervised learning uses labelled training data to learn the mapping function turning input variables (X) into output (Y).
Focusing on Classification and Regression</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install m10c theme.</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:29 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/theme/</guid>
      <description>Your m10c theme from ZERO to one This is a short tutorial to help us building a Hugo blog with m10c theme. This memo has four parts as following:Part 1 - Pre tools setting Part 2 - Build a Hugo framework Part 3 - Host on GitHub Part 4 - Final Step Part 5 - Real Final Step Reference </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:48:07 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to post Hugo content</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:43:22 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/hugo/</guid>
      <description>How to post a Hugo markdown AND Chinese Testing 中文測試 How to post a Hugo content Step 1: To enter into your blog root folder, ie, &amp;lsquo;blog&amp;rsquo; in my case:
$ cd hugo $ hugo Step 2: create a new post(markdown format title.md) by
$ hugo new post/title.md And then please your familiar text editor to complete your content writing and save. My favourite editor for GitHub writing is Atom IDE and Vim command line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Categories</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:38:42 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/categories/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:38:33 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/tags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 23:17:29 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/post/content/</guid>
      <description>Hello World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://elliottsao.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 17:12:17 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elliottsao.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>中文 我叫Elliott，來自澳洲的墨爾本，是一名醫療數據分析師，業餘天文攝影師，同時是一名公共衛生專業的研究式碩士，即將讀本專業的博士，研究領域為&amp;quot;流行病學與機器學習疾病偵測&amp;quot;。我的其他興趣包括：天文、物理、醫療以及哲學，比如說，我在學拉丁文、德文和法文。
這個Hugo部落格是我在2020年繼Hexo部落格之後的第二個 開始使用這種部落格的初衷是為了紀錄日常使用的一些代碼、錯誤紀錄和好的想法。
最後：我的hugo部落格之旅從此開始 AND 我的征途是星辰大海！！！
Deutsch Ich heiße Elliott und komme aus Melbourne. Ich bin ein Gesundheitsdatenanalyst, Astro-Fotograf und ein Meister der Philosophie im Bereich der öffentlichen Gesundheit. Interessen sind Astronomie, Physik, Gesundheit und Philosophie. Deshalb lerne ich auch Latina Lingua, Deutsch und Französisch.
Dieser Hugo-Blog ist mein zweiter Blog nach dem ersten Hexo zu Beginn dieses Jahres. Der Hauptgrund, warum wir Hugo endlich starten, ist das Aufzeichnen von Codes und nützlichen Fähigkeiten beim maschinellen Lernen und dergleichen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
